CURRICULUMN VITAE

NORBERT GUDA

Personal Profile Statement

I'm an IT graduate and a certified data scientist, with an experience in programming related to web development. I also have two years of experience working in cyber; providing cyber services, as well as hardware and network troubleshooting and maintenance. I'm a motivated, adaptive, responsible, reliable and honest person to work with in a team.

Personal Info

Name : Norbert Oluoch Guda

Phone No : 0713627929

Email : norbertguda94@gmail.com

Address : P.O Box 155-40101

Languages : English and Kiswahili

Projects

- Personal Portfolio (in progress)
- Fitness website
- Blog website

Experience

Currently : Freelancer – computer maintenance and services

(software and hardware installation).

Jan 2022 - April 2022 : IT intern, United States International University-Africa.

Jan 2014 - Dec 2016 : Computer services and maintenance, ALYMAX CYBER.

2013 : Phone repair trainee, Faustin's Phone Repair Shop

Kisumu.

Education

2017 - 2021 : Diploma in Computer Technology,

Technical University of Kenya.

2009 - 2012 : Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (KCSE)

Mean grade of B-

Otieno Oyoo Secondary School.

2001 – 2008 : Kenya Certificate of Secondary Education (KCPE)

302 Marks

Bwanda Primary School

Certifications

Currently: Certificate in Software Engineering, ALX

2021 : Certificate in Data Science (TUK)

2013 : KEPSA-KYOP Youths Training Skills

Hobbies

Reading books

Interacting

Watching football

References

Luke Okello Lecturer, Technical University of Kenya 0723650683

Bernard Agalo Owner, Alymax Computers Cyber 0714281891

Eric Kemei

Trainer, United State International University-Africa (USIU) 0724746171